Today I ordered a new product
from Kriti Sanon's brand That's Huffy Double
Shot Radiance Lift Serum.  Let's see if this works
or not.  The packaging was quite cool.
It offers the power and benefits of not one, but two serums.
My skin is oily and
a little uneven too.  So that's why I
ordered this product.  Just shake the bottle
and apply it on your face
and neck.  This is not any paid promotion guys.
I'm literally testing this on my
skin.  Whenever I apply serum or any
product, I
massage it a little on my face and neck so that
blood circulation also happens because
we do not have time throughout the day, okay it gets
absorbed quickly in the skin, look at it I can
feel the hydration on the skin,
you will find the link of this product on this video,
you can shop from here and for more
such videos follow for more